The sky cracked open at
7:03 p.m.
Every screen on Earth
went black.
Then one sentence
appeared.
EARTH HAS FAILED.
A mysterious voice
announced the Dominion
Trial.
Ninety-nine humans would
be chosen as Lords.
Every piece of land they
claimed and built would
become humanity's next
home.
Failure meant death.
Success meant survival.
Everyone expected
soldiers, scientists,
and survival experts.
Instead, the system
chose Maya Lin.
A nineteen-year-old girl
eating instant noodles
in her messy apartment.
Seconds later, her room
vanished.
She woke up barefoot on
a deserted beach.
Behind her was the
ocean.
In front of her was a
dark forest.
A blue screen appeared.
PLAYER 47 SELECTED.
MISSION: SURVIVE.
CLAIM LAND.
BUILD A TERRITORY.
On Earth, billions
watched her live stream.
The comments were
merciless.
"She's useless."
"She won't survive one
night."
"Humanity is doomed."
Maya could not see them.
She only saw the tide
rising toward her feet.
No food.
No knife.
No shoes.
No one to save her.
For one moment, she
wanted to cry.
Then she remembered her
grandmother's words.
"Move first.
Panic later."
So Maya turned away from
the ocean...
and walked into the
forest.
Everyone thought she
would die by morning.
They were wrong.